Hey, she's not as pretty as she was
when she was 29.
Miss Green would like to establish some ground
rules before she comes out.
She would appreciate it if you didn't use
the words old or downhill or they still
look pretty damn good.
They do.
Rachel, come on out.
Monica made breakfast.
Chocolate chip pancakes.
We've got presents.
Good ones?
They all came from the list you handed
out to us two weeks ago.
Well, can I keep the presents and still
be 29?
Come on, Rach.
Look, turn it this way.
30 is not that big a deal.
Oh, really?
Is that how you felt when you turned
30?
Why, God, why?
We had a deal.
Let the others grow old, not me.
You know, I'm still 29 in Guam.
Hey, 30 is not that old.
Do you know how old the Earth is?
Late 30s?
Oh, come on, you guys.
Is it just me?
Am I overreacting to this?
No, Rach.
It's not just you.
My 30th birthday certainly wasn't that much fun.
And now Chandler.
We're all getting so old.
Why are you doing this to us?
Rach, you're in a great place in your
life.
I mean, come on.
You have an amazing job.
Good friends.
Yeah.
Your roommate's a soap opera star.
Your character's in a coma.
I promised myself I wasn't going to cry
at this one.
Look, you know, I know my life's going
pretty well, but I look around and I
just see so many people who've accomplished so
many of their goals by the time they're
30.
Yeah, but you shouldn't compare yourself to me.
Come on.
OK, come on, baby.
Let's do it, baby.
Come on.
There you go.
Yes, yes, yes.
I did it.
One mile on a hippity hop.
That's it.
That's everything I wanted to do before I
was 30.
Oh, except I wanted to patch things up
with my sister.
Oh, well.
But yeah.
And girls, this thing is a godsend.
If you know what I mean.
30.
Oh, I mean 30.
Monica, you remember mean old Mrs. Krieger in
the 5th grade?
She was 30.
Let's have some fun, huh?
What do you want to do today?
Nothing.
I don't want to do anything.
Yeah, doing nothing on your 30th is better
than doing something stupid, like Ross.
Hey, that was a practical purchase.
I needed that car for transportation.
OK?
I have a child.
How hot do I look in this, huh?
Ross, a sports car?
Wouldn't it be cheaper to just stuff a
sock down there?
That's not what this is about, OK?
I am a sports car enthusiast.
I've always been into cars.
Hey, what's the horsepower on this thing?
I don't know, but look how shiny.
I can't believe you bought this.
Really?
God, Ross, what were you thinking?
I know it's really shallow, but a part
of me wants him again.
Oh, well, get in line, missy.
So, can I have a ride, stud?
Hop in.
Get ready for the smoothest ride of your
life.
Damn it!
OK, who's next?
You know what?
I am going to do something today.
I'm not just going to sit around like
some old lady.
I'm going to get something pierced.
Like my nose or my tongue or something.
Really?
Because, you know, that hurts.
So what?
You know what, the way I see it...
Ow!
Son of a bitch!
Look, Rachel, I know what you're going through.
I'm totally freaked out about turning 25.
Get out of my apartment.
Rachel, for what it's worth, I think that
you're doing great.
I mean, you know, let's face it, no
one handles this well.
At least of all you.
Why?
What'd you do?
Weren't you asked to leave, Sonny?
Oh, would you put that back on?
Monica's going to be here any minute.
But it hurts my Joey's apple.
OK, for the last time, it's not named
after each individual man.
You've done a wonderful job with this party,
Chandler.
Everything looks so lovely.
Oh, well, not as lovely as you.
I mean, I can't believe it.
I can't believe that you would have a
30-year-old daughter.
And you, I can't believe that you would
have a tux that's 30 years old.
It's older than that.
Ross was actually conceived right near this tuxedo.
Oh.
Wait, everybody, hide, hide.
I saw her, she's coming.
OK, OK, everybody down.
Everybody down.
Crap.
OK, everybody stay here.
I will find out what's going on.
Hey, you got a tux.
Hey, are you drunk?
No.
OK.
See, I was a little nervous about turning...
30.
So the buzz boys took me out for
some drinks.
I want to puke on you later.
OK, here's the thing.
We have thrown a very formal surprise party
for you in there.
All your friends are in there and your
parents.
Yes.
No.
Oh, no, my parents have never seen me
drunk.
That they know of.
Here's the thing.
We're going to get you some coffee and
they will never know that you're drunk.
Really, you promise?
Yes, I'll take care of it.
I love you so much.
OK, we have to do something about your
breath.
What about your breath?
That's still yours.
OK, now remember, it's a surprise party.
So when you go in, act surprised.
Ready?
Surprise!
OK, forward.
Forward, stop.
OK, back, stop.
OK.
Stop, stop, stop.
Ross, just forget about it.
The guy's got you totally wedged in.
Is this yours?
No, no, it's mine.
It's mine.
Dude, you so need this car.
OK, OK, here's what we're going to do,
OK?
I'm going to break into this minivan.
Put it in neutral.
You guys push it forward so Ross can
drive out of the spot.
OK?
OK.
All right, here we go.
Happy 30th birthday.
Here.
It's for the child in you.
And the woman.
Happy 30th.
Right, why do you keep saying that?
Because it's our 30th birthday.
Yeah, no, we're not 30, we're 31.
OK.
Wait.
Oh, it's you.
Yeah.
What?
Yeah, we're not 30, we're 31.
Nuh-uh.
Uh-huh.
That's what it says on my birth certificate.
You have your birth certificate?
Yeah, I got a big box of family
stuff when my mom died.
Our mom.
Right, OK.
Do you have my birth certificate?
No, I sold it to a Swedish runaway.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, we are 31.
Yeah.
I just lost a whole year of my
life.
OK.
Your middle name is Pamela?
Yes.
I never knew mine.
Do you remember what it is?
Yes.
Phoebe.
That's my first name.
Right, OK.
Then no.
Look at that, we made it all the
way across the room.
You're doing great.
What's going on?
Monica's a little drunk.
Yay, I love drunk Monica.
Oh, she's so much more fun than regular
Monica.
She doesn't want her parents to know she's
drunk.
Oh, all right, all right.
Here's what we'll do.
I'll get twice as drunk as Monica, and
then no one's even going to notice her.
Drunk Phoebe's mean.
OK, you watch your tone with me.
What's going on?
Monica's wasted.
Maybe that'll liven up this party.
Can't we just go help her get changed,
please?
OK, but taking care of a drunk naked
woman seems like a job for Joey.
Yeah.
This one's from me.
It wasn't on your list, but hopefully you'll
think it's really fun.
A scooter.
Stick to the list.
Always stick to the list.
Oh, no, no, I love it, thank you.
OK, open ours next, open ours next.
OK.
Now that you're a couple, we don't get
two presents from you guys?
For my last birthday, you gave me a
hug.
OK, read the card, read the card.
OK.
Happy birthday, Grandma.
Over the hill.
Then buried under it.
Oh, I love Monica Chandler, that's funny.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, that was a joke.
No, I know, I get it, it's funny.
No, because you're not a grandmother.
No, I know, because to be a grandmother,
you have to be married and have children,
and I don't have any of those things.
That's why it's so funny.
I'm just gonna go.
All you had to do was buy the
card.
Hey, look who's back, it's the birthday girl.
How's the birthday girl feeling?
Well, I feel fine, but I think you're
bumming out the rest of the kids.
What?
OK, you know what?
I realize it was stupid to get upset
about not having a husband and kids.
All I really needed was a plan.
See, I want to have three kids.
Well, let me guess, and you want to
have them all at the same time, and
you want to have them for your brother.
As I was saying, I should probably have
the first of the three kids by the
time I'm 35, right?
Which gives me five years.
I love this plan, I want to marry
this plan.
You could do that, I'd marry the hippity
hop.
So if I want to have a kid
when I'm 35, I don't have to get
pregnant until I'm 34, which gives Prada four
years to start making maternity clothes.
Oh, wait, but...
Now, I do want to be married for
a year before I get pregnant.
Really?
That long?
Look all you want, it's happening.
Now, so I don't have to get married
until I'm 33.
That's three years, that's three whole years.
Oh, wait a minute, though.
I'll need a year and a half to
plan the wedding.
And I'd like to know the guy for
like a year, year and a half before
we get engaged, which means I need to
meet the guy by the time I'm 30.
Which is fine, because you just turned 28!
No, Ross, no, it is not fine.
According to my plan, I should already be
with the guy that I'm gonna marry.
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, you quit hogging it!
Oh, I'm telling you, it's like watching Bambi
learn how to walk.
You're drunk.
Mom and Dad are gonna be mad.
Maybe I'm a little drunk.
Hey, are those crab cakes?
Did I not tell you to come straight
to me when more crab cakes were ready?
How are you feeling?
You are so handsome.
I wanna make love to you right here,
right now.
I really wish that you wouldn't.
Now, all you have to do is just
get through a little bit more, okay?
Then we can put you in bed, okay?
Just smile, and don't talk to anyone.
Speech!
Let's hear from the birthday girl, huh?
Don't you see?
Everybody's looking at me.
The plan's working.
I didn't even have to take off my
top yet.
Speech!
Come on, Mom.
Hey, Chandler, you can't keep your hands off
her for one second.
Oh, I think it's nice.
I think it's necessary.
I wanna thank you all for coming.
My family and my friends.
Speech!
I'd really like to say that I'm, um...
You know what I'd really like to say?
I'm drunk!
That's right, Mom, is hammered!
More!
And I've smoked a cigarette.
And I've got a box of ding-dongs
hidden in my underwear drawer.
It's all okay.
It's okay, because I turned 30 today.
And I can do anything I want.
Because I am a grown-up.
Okay, quick, help me get this off.
Yeah.
I lost a whole year.
I can't believe it.
This is so unfair.
Come on, Pheebs, it'll be okay.
Will it?
How would you feel if you found out
you were 31?
That's not gonna happen.
No, because we have a new deal.
Plus, it totally ruined my schedule.
I...
I haven't done any of the things I
wanted to do by the time I was
31.
Like what?
Like, okay, I...
I...
I haven't met any Portuguese people.
I haven't had the perfect kiss.
And I haven't been to sniper school.
Baby, you know what?
Why don't we just go upstairs and have
some birthday cake?
No, I just feel like being by myself
for a while.
All right, I'll see you guys later.
Thanks.
Oh, poor Pheebs.
Hey, you know what, you guys?
I think I'm gonna go walk her home.
Oh, man.
What?
He's gonna eat the cake.
Pheebs, get up.
Listen, uh...
Close your eyes.
If that's one thing you can cross off
your list.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, and plus, I'm 1 16th Portuguese.
Okay, is everybody clear?
We're gonna pick it up...
And move it.
All we need is teamwork, okay?
We're gonna lift the car...
And slide it out.
Lift...
And slide.
Ross, I really don't think...
Lift...
And slide.
All right.
Come on, dogs.
Let's lift this sucker.
Oh, unless you're scared.
Oh, little weakling scared.
Good teamwork.
Okay, here we go.
All right, everyone.
Lift...
And slide.
Well, come on, Rach.
My turn just started.
Actually, I just want to talk to Ted.
Oh, okay.
Hey.
Can I ride this outside?
Whatever, okay?
I'm not your mother.
Okay.
Not in the street, Brooklyn!
Hey.
How you doing?
Are you feeling any better?
Yeah, I'm doing okay.
I'm...
Um...
Let's talk.
Okay.
Um...
What's up?
Oh, Ted, um...
You're such a great guy.
And we have so much fun together.
But I...
Wait.
I think I see where you're going.
But before you say anything else, can I
just say one more thing?
Well said.
And a good example of the fun I
was referring to.
Uh, but...
I just think I'm past the point where
I can, you know, just have fun.
Rachel, don't do this.
This is just because you're turning 30.
Yeah, it is.
But you're just a kid.
I mean, you're...
You're 25.
24, actually.
Oh, God.
You know what I wish?
I wish you were six years older.
Well, actually, if I'm wishing for stuff, I
actually wish I was six years younger.
Me too.
Yeah, sorry.
Sorry.
Hey, let it go.
Oh.
If I only want two kids, can I
keep him for another year?
You did the right thing.
I don't like this anymore.
Well, here we are.
Just a bunch of 30-year-olds.
Wow, do you realize in 10 years, we're
gonna be 40?
Why, God?
Why are you doing this to us?
Yes!
My baby's finally free!
Right.
Start it up.
Let's go.
Woo-hoo!
How hot are we?
Hmm?
You wanna buy a car?
No.